

SKILLS

- Bootstrap, JQuery, Javascript, CSS and HTML
- Wordpress with Elementor
- Data Entry
- Customer Service
- Social Media Manager
- · ConnectWise Email Marketing

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Virtual Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the outsourcing/offshoring industry and also in web development industry for more than 4 years by developing websites using Bootstrap, Javascript, CSS, HTML and jQuery and mostly front-end development. I'm using Wordpress as CMS and Elementor as web page builder.

WORK HISTORY

Virtual Assistant

Upwork | July 2015 - present

Account Executive in Sales Department

- Submitting quotes to customers
- · Process purchase orders
- Tracking orders

Customer Service Representative

Transcom Iloilo | February 2015 - May 2015

- Inbound calls for billing inquiries from customers
- Selling Cable, Internet and Phone Services

Web Developer

Sell2Any B.V. | June 2014 - November 2014

Convert PSD web design into HTML file using bootstrap

Web Developer

HPO Phil., Inc. | October 2013 - March 2014

Helped Team developed Funnel Websites using WordPress

Software Programmer

Geodata Solutions Inc. | July 2009 - September 2013

Helped Team developed the Hospital Information System

- Design the graphical user interface of every module
- Writing backend codes
- Tests the system for quality assurance.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

University of Southern Mindanao | March 2009

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email: markozpaez1525@gmail.com **Website:** https://markozpaez.netlify.app

Contact: +639281274145 Address: Jaro, Iloilo City